[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When we find the extrema of a function we use this.", "correct_answer": "The first derivative", "incorrect_answers": ["The solution of the sixth degree equation", "The solution of the second degree equation", "The third derivative"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Don Paz passenger ferry was on its way to what island in 1987 when it collided with an oil tanker?", "correct_answer": "Philippines", "incorrect_answers": ["Thailand", "Jamaica", "Singapore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these products takes more than 30 years to biodegrade?", "correct_answer": "Nylon fabric", "incorrect_answers": ["Cigarette filters", "Leather shoes", "Paper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie is the following tag line from: EARTH Take a good look. It could be your last.", "correct_answer": "Independence Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Evolution", "Mars Attacks!", "Armageddon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the role of Thomas Sams in the movie Lean on Me?", "correct_answer": "Jermaine Hopkins", "incorrect_answers": ["Cedric The Entertainer", "Anthony Anderson", "Wish of B.O.N.E Thugs n Harmony"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous painter, a representative of the romantic period, delivered the following words: Artists who seek perfection in everything are those who cannot attain it in anything.", "correct_answer": "Delacroix", "incorrect_answers": ["Picasso", "Modigliani", "Renoir"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the following Irish saying: However long the day it ends with _______.", "correct_answer": "night", "incorrect_answers": ["some bread", "a lullaby", "a bang"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the predominant mood of a person with anxiety?", "correct_answer": "Fear", "incorrect_answers": ["Anger", "Sadness", "Loneliness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dirty Dancing, who is Billy related to and how?", "correct_answer": "Johnny (cousin)", "incorrect_answers": ["Penny (brother)", "Johnny (brother)", "Max (nephew)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The so-called space of Disse is located in this internal organ of the human body.", "correct_answer": "Liver", "incorrect_answers": ["Spleen", "Pancreas", "Kidney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This unlicensed version of Bram Stokers Dracula was so similar to the novel that it was ordered to be destroyed after Bram Stokers estate sued.", "correct_answer": "Nosferutu (1922)", "incorrect_answers": ["Dracula (1931)", "Blacula (1972)", "Vampyres (1974)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ube is a shade of this color.", "correct_answer": "Lavender", "incorrect_answers": ["Brick", "Mustard", "Olive"]}]